<resources>
    <string name="app_name">About Me</string>
    <string name="name">Leonardo da Vinci</string>
    <string name="yellow_star">Yellow star</string>
    <string name="bio">
        Leonardo da Vinci (English: /ˌliːəˈnɑːrdoʊ də ˈvɪntʃi, ˌliːoʊˈ-, ˌleɪoʊˈ-/;a 14/15 April 1452b – 2 May 1519),4 was an Italian polymath of the High
        Renaissance who is widely considered one of the greatest painters of all time (despite less than 25 of his paintings having survived).c The Mona
        Lisa is the most famous of Leonardo\'s works and the most famous portrait ever made.5 The Last Supper is the most reproduced religious painting of
        all time6 and his Vitruvian Man drawing is also regarded as a cultural icon.7 He is also known for his his notebooks, in which he made drawings
        and notes on science and invention; these involve a variety of subjects including anatomy, cartography, painting, and paleontology. Leonardos
        collective works compose a contribution to later generations of artists rivalled only by that of his contemporary Michelangelo.

        Properly named Leonardo di ser Piero da Vinci,d Leonardo was born out of wedlock to a notary, Piero da Vinci, and a peasant woman, Caterina, in
        Vinci, in the region of Florence, Italy. Leonardo was educated in the studio of the renowned Italian painter Andrea del Verrocchio. Much of his
        earlier working life was spent in the service of Ludovico il Moro in Milan, and he later worked in Rome, Bologna and Venice. He spent his last
        three years in France, where he died in 1519.

        Although he had no formal academic training,9 many historians and scholars regard Leonardo as the prime exemplar of the "Universal Genius" or
        "Renaissance Man", an individual of "unquenchable curiosity" and "feverishly inventive imagination."6 He is widely considered one of the most
        diversely talented individuals ever to have lived.10 According to art historian Helen Gardner, the scope and depth of his interests were
        without precedent in recorded history, and "his mind and personality seem to us superhuman, while the man himself mysterious and remote."6
        Scholars interpret his view of the world as being based in logic, though the empirical methods he used were unorthodox for his time.
    </string>
    <string name="what_is_your_nickname">What is your nickname?</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
</resources>